aragon-advertising.com 2016-11-21

# Privacy | Aragon Advertising

##### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to the use of aragon-advertising.com.  
We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site.

##### Log Files and Cookies

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you have submitted while on our site.

##### Links to Other Websites

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

##### Registration and Use of Personal Information

Registration is not required in order to use or access this website.

##### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer wish us to possess your information, you may request correction, updating, or deletion of your information by emailing us at [support@aragon-advertising.com](mailto:support@aragon-advertising.com). You may also complete any corrections, updates or deletion requests at [http://publishers.aragon-advertising.com](http://publishers.aragon-advertising.com/); you also may make your request by phone or postal mail at the address/phone number indicated at the end of this privacy policy.

##### Security

We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us.  
You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by emailing us at [support@aragon-advertising.com](mailto:support@aragon-advertising.com)

##### Links to Other Websites

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

##### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website.

##### Contact Details

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us by phone or postal mail, our contact information is as follows:  

1115 Broadway  
10th Floor  
New York, NY, 10010  
This privacy policy was last updated on Dec 11th, 2014.
